export const helpData = [
   {
      category: "",
      question: "What is QualKey?",
      answer: "QualKey provides secure digital credentials so you can prove the authenticity of your qualification. Through QualKey, you can store evidence of your qualification on a personal device, and you control what, and with whom, information is shared."
   },
   {
      category: "",
      question: "What are digital credentials?",
      answer: "Digital credentials are the information that underpin your qualification, such as the start, end, and graduation date for your qualification, along with the name of the issuing educational institution. Additional credentials may be available depending on the educational institution."
   },
   {
      category: "student",
      question: "How does QualKey authenticate my qualifications?",
      answer: "QualKey partners directly with educational institutions. On completion of your qualification, the institution provides Qualkey with digital credentials confirming you are entitled to receive the qualification. "
   },
   {
      category: "student",
      question: "Why do I need to activate my digital credentials?",
      answer: "On completion of your qualification, your educational institution provides QualKey with the digital credentials underpinning your qualification. You will need to activate your credentials in order to share them with third parties."
   },
   {
      category: "student",
      question: "Can I view my original qualification certificate?",
      answer: "QualKey does not store your original certificate. Instead, QualKey stores the digital credentials that underpin your qualification. These credentials form a permanent record that can be shared, as many times as you like, with whoever you give permission to. "
   },
   {
      category: "student",
      question: "Who can I share my qualification credentials with?",
      answer: "You can share your digital credentials with anyone you choose by email. This saves time and effort in verifying your qualifications."
   },
   {
      category: "student",
      question: "Do I need to pay a subscription?",
      answer: "Absolutely not. QualKey charges a one-off payment for each qualification that provides access for 10 years. During the next decade, you can share as many times as you like without incurring further charges. "
   },
   {
      question: "How do I contact QualKey?",
      answer: "We welcome your feedback and insights. If you have any questions or comments, please contact us at info@qualkey.org or leave a message via our website www.qualkey.org "
   },
   {
      question: "Does QualKey use blockchain?",
      answer: "No. QualKey uses decentralised ledger technology along with Hedera Hashgraph to create a secure, permanent and immutable record of your qualification. In addition to your digital credentials, QualKey provides a record of your Hedera Hashgraph ID, so that your qualification can independently be verified if required. "
   },
   {
      category: "student",
      question: "Why have I been asked by my educational institution to register for a QualKey account?",
      answer: "QualKey has partnered with your educational institution to provide secure digital credentials that prove your qualification is authentic. Your credentials can be shared instantly with employers or other educational institutions who may ask you to show your qualification is genuine. "
   },
   {
      question: "About QualKey?",
      answer: "QualKey was founded by three friends who met whilst studying. They believed that proving to educational institutions and employers that their qualifications were genuine was cumbersome and inefficient. The result, QualKey was born. "
   }
]